<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives - Share Sports</title>
	<atom:link href="https://share.js.org/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://share.js.org/category/news/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 18:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://share.js.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/cropped-iqa_logo-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News Archives - Share Sports</title>
	<link>https://share.js.org/category/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Liverpool twice fought back with 10 men to deny Fulham</title>
		<link>https://share.js.org/liverpool-twice-fought-back-with-10-men-to-deny-fulham/</link>
					<comments>https://share.js.org/liverpool-twice-fought-back-with-10-men-to-deny-fulham/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 18:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://share.js.org/?p=98</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The returning Diogo Jota scored a late equaliser as Premier League leaders Liverpool twice fought back with 10 men to&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://share.js.org/liverpool-twice-fought-back-with-10-men-to-deny-fulham/">Liverpool twice fought back with 10 men to deny Fulham</a> appeared first on <a href="https://share.js.org/">Share Sports</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The returning Diogo Jota scored a late equaliser as Premier League leaders Liverpool twice fought back with 10 men to deny Fulham following Andy Robertson&#8217;s red card at Anfield.</p>
<p>Jota, sidelined with injury since October, slotted in an 86th-minute leveller after Rodrigo Muniz looked to have ended the Reds&#8217; second-half resistance.</p>
<p>Cody Gakpo&#8217;s header from Mohamed Salah&#8217;s sublime cross shortly after half-time had cancelled out Andreas Pereira&#8217;s 11th-minute opener.</p>
<p>Six minutes after Pereira volleyed Fulham ahead, Liverpool&#8217;s task became even tougher when Robertson was dismissed for denying Harry Wilson a goalscoring opportunity.</p>
<p>While Fulham centre-back Issa Diop had earlier escaped with a booking for a high challenge on the offside Robertson, there was no such fortune for the Liverpool left-back and a lengthy video assistant referee (VAR) review confirmed Wilson was onside before pouncing on his mistake.</p>
<p>After Wilson fizzed the resulting free-kick narrowly over Alisson&#8217;s goal, Liverpool reset and continued to cause Fulham problems &#8211; but Luis Diaz headed over the hosts&#8217; best chance before half-time.</p>
<p>However, a re-energised Liverpool stormed out of the blocks in the second half and Gakpo&#8217;s instant leveller after the restart sparked the Anfield crowd into life.</p>
<p>Fulham&#8217;s failure to capitalise on their numerical advantage fuelled Liverpool&#8217;s belief and Salah twice went close to completing the turnaround but could not find the target before Muniz delivered a sucker punch.</p>
<p>There was to be one final twist late in an enthralling contest when Jota marked his return with a fine finish to set up a chaotic, breathless conclusion, with both sides made to settle for a point.</p>
<p>After a thrilling 3-3 draw with Newcastle 10 days ago, Liverpool&#8217;s title rivals were able to make up further ground after last weekend&#8217;s Merseyside derby against Everton was postponed by severe weather.</p>
<p>But they extended their lead over Chelsea, who host Brentford on Sunday, to five points after third-place Arsenal were held to a goalless draw by Everton.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://share.js.org/liverpool-twice-fought-back-with-10-men-to-deny-fulham/">Liverpool twice fought back with 10 men to deny Fulham</a> appeared first on <a href="https://share.js.org/">Share Sports</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://share.js.org/liverpool-twice-fought-back-with-10-men-to-deny-fulham/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The red-carpet dress made from upcycled rowing kits</title>
		<link>https://share.js.org/the-red-carpet-dress-made-from-upcycled-rowing-kits/</link>
					<comments>https://share.js.org/the-red-carpet-dress-made-from-upcycled-rowing-kits/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://share.js.org/?p=92</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Olympic rowing champion Imogen Grant walks down the red carpet at Sports Personality of the Year on Tuesday, she&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://share.js.org/the-red-carpet-dress-made-from-upcycled-rowing-kits/">The red-carpet dress made from upcycled rowing kits</a> appeared first on <a href="https://share.js.org/">Share Sports</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Olympic rowing champion Imogen Grant walks down the red carpet at Sports Personality of the Year on Tuesday, she will be wearing a special dress.</p>
<p>It is the result of a unique project which enabled Grant to combine her passions for sustainability with high fashion.</p>
<p>The 28-year old, who was named BBC Green Sports Awards Athlete of the Year, donated her old sports kits to the London College of Fashion so they could be upcycled into a dress she will wear at the awards.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think it&#8217;s an amazing project, and I really hope it sends a message,&#8221; said Grant, who won gold in Paris alongside Emily Craig in the women&#8217;s lightweight double sculls.</p>
<p>&#8220;As athletes we get given lots of kit and so much of it gets wasted. As soon as a sponsor changes, a whole new set comes in.</p>
<p>&#8220;I hope this shows there&#8217;s another life it can have. The way we make kit at the moment is just not sustainable.&#8221;</p>
<p>It took two months to create the dress, with maker Aishvarya Verma facing several technical challenges.</p>
<p>&#8220;We had to work with lots of different fabrics that weren&#8217;t manufactured for an evening dress,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>&#8220;But I would say the hardest part was taking the pieces apart because we did not want to waste anything.&#8221;</p>
<p>Six items of kit have been used in the final design &#8211; each with a story to tell &#8211; and it took Verma seven days to unpick the stitching of just one of them.</p>
<p>&#8220;The front section is the kit I wore when I won the gold medal in Paris,&#8221; said Grant. &#8220;There&#8217;s kit that I raced in and trained in when I was a newbie on the GB team.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve set world-best times wearing some of it, and they&#8217;ve even used part of the jacket I wore for the opening ceremony at the Tokyo Olympics.</p>
<p>&#8220;Back in October, when I handed over a big bag of kit I had no idea how they were going to transform it &#8211; but they&#8217;ve been worked into a red-carpet look.&#8221;</p>
<p>Verma said: &#8220;We wanted to blend her memories into one dress.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://share.js.org/the-red-carpet-dress-made-from-upcycled-rowing-kits/">The red-carpet dress made from upcycled rowing kits</a> appeared first on <a href="https://share.js.org/">Share Sports</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://share.js.org/the-red-carpet-dress-made-from-upcycled-rowing-kits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Northampton show outstanding spirit to beat Bulls</title>
		<link>https://share.js.org/northampton-show-outstanding-spirit-to-beat-bulls/</link>
					<comments>https://share.js.org/northampton-show-outstanding-spirit-to-beat-bulls/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 18:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://share.js.org/?p=86</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investec Champions Cup Bulls (7) 21 Tries: Coetzee, Hanekom 2 Cons: Goosen 3 Northampton (12) 30 Tries: Hendy, Augustus, Freeman&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://share.js.org/northampton-show-outstanding-spirit-to-beat-bulls/">Northampton show outstanding spirit to beat Bulls</a> appeared first on <a href="https://share.js.org/">Share Sports</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investec Champions Cup</p>
<p>Bulls (7) 21</p>
<p>Tries: Coetzee, Hanekom 2 Cons: Goosen 3</p>
<p>Northampton (12) 30</p>
<p>Tries: Hendy, Augustus, Freeman 2 Cons: Smith 2 Pens: Smith 2</p>
<p>Tommy Freeman scored two tries as Northampton produced a display of outstanding spirit in the altitude and heat to earn a Champions Cup bonus-point win over Bulls in South Africa.</p>
<p>The victory keeps up Northampton&#8217;s perfect start in Pool Three, with two wins from two and a maximum 10 points.</p>
<p>In physically demanding conditions in Pretoria, the Saints held out in the face of the Bulls&#8217; power, and rode the loss of captain George Furbank with an arm injury, to lead just after the half-hour mark through George Hendy.</p>
<p>The full-back, barely on for two minutes as Furbank&#8217;s replacement, took on Fin Smith&#8217;s offload after Fraser Dingwall had charged at the Bulls defence.</p>
<p>Bulls were quickly in front as Marcell Coetzee evaded Dingwall&#8217;s tackle and pumped through to score a try converted by Johan Goosen.</p>
<p>Northampton faced a further setback right at the end of the first half when prop Emmanuel Iyogun was sent to the sin-bin.</p>
<p>But with the first-half clock in the red, and barely a minute after being reduced to 14 players, the visitors restored their lead as Alex Mitchell took a quick tap penalty and opened up the Bulls defence for Juarno Augustus to go over in the corner.</p>
<p>The Bulls had seen two tries ruled out in an opening half hour where they somehow failed to turn their physical dominance into points &#8211; and then another disallowed early in the second half as Canan Moodie failed to ground the ball as he chased a kick through.</p>
<p>Smith extended the lead with a penalty, before Freeman capitalised on a line-out to burst through David Kriel&#8217;s tackle &#8211; with the television match official ruling that he had managed to get the ball down.</p>
<p>But Cameron Hanekom surged out of a scrum and bounced off the referee to evade Mitchell and score to give the hosts hope.</p>
<p>Then the number eight repeated the trick to bring the hosts back to within a point with 10 minutes left.</p>
<p>Smith took advantage of the altitude to land a penalty almost from halfway, and was narrowly off target with a drop-goal attempt from nearly as far out &#8211; before Freeman dived over again in the final four minutes to seal a bonus point and a memorable victory.</p>
<p>Saints demonstrate heart as Bulls waste chances<br />
The Premiership champions, who have struggled for form domestically so far this season, began their European campaign with a 38-8 victory over an under-strength Castres last weekend, but this was a very different test.</p>
<p>In temperatures topping 30C in Pretoria, they had to work hard just to hang on for the opening half hour, suffering a setback when Furbank was forced off, using his shirt as a makeshift sling to cradle his right arm after being clattered by Bulls captain Elrigh Louw.</p>
<p>Northampton were undoubtedly helped in the early stages by Bulls&#8217; lack of ruthlessness. The hosts may have dominated physically, causing the visitors all sorts of trouble in the scrum, but failed to convert that into points when the door appeared to be wide open.</p>
<p>The Saints conceded four penalties in the opening 15 minutes &#8211; with Iyogun twice penalised for collapsing the scrum &#8211; and twice escaped as their hosts had tries ruled out, while Goosen also dropped the ball barely a couple of metres from the line.</p>
<p>That came after Devon Williams had gone clear from an Embrose Papier pass over the top to dive in at the corner &#8211; with Goosen actually adding the conversion before the try was pulled back for review and ruled out because of an obstruction by Willie le Roux.</p>
<p>Then former Sale hooker Akker van der Merwe darted over to dot down, but referee Luc Ramos had already blown his whistle for an obstruction by JF van Heerden.</p>
<p>Northampton lost Iyogun, yet not only negotiated his 10-minute absence without conceding any points, but also turned a deficit into a lead through Augustus&#8217; score.</p>
<p>The Bulls&#8217; attacking profligacy haunted them again as Moodie and Le Roux chased a kick over the top, with the centre just winning the race &#8211; but as Goosen was lining up the kick, the television match official was called in once more, and ruled that the ball had not been grounded.</p>
<p>When Freeman extended the Northampton lead to 22-7, the win looked there for the taking &#8211; but there was always the danger they would tire in the heat, and the impressive Hanekom&#8217;s double score increased their anxiety.</p>
<p>It was to Northampton&#8217;s credit that they did not wilt, and Smith and Freeman took the match out of the hosts&#8217; reach.</p>
<p>Line-ups<br />
Bulls: Le Roux, De Klerk, Moodie, Kriel, Williams; Goosen, Papier; Steenekamp, Van der Merwe, Louw, Vermaak, Van Heerden, Coetzee, Louw (capt), Hanekom.</p>
<p>Replacements: Wessels, Tshakweni, Klopper, Slabbert, Nama Xaba, Burger, Chamberlain, Gans.</p>
<p>Northampton: Furbank (capt); Freeman, Dingwall, Hutchinson, Sleightholme; Smith, Mitchell; Iyogun, Langdon, Millar-Mills, Mayanavanua, Lockett, Coles, Pollock, Augustus.</p>
<p>Replacements: Wright, Haffar, Davison, Munga, Scott-Young, Pearson, McParland, Hendy.</p>
<p>Referee: Luc Ramos (France)</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://share.js.org/northampton-show-outstanding-spirit-to-beat-bulls/">Northampton show outstanding spirit to beat Bulls</a> appeared first on <a href="https://share.js.org/">Share Sports</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://share.js.org/northampton-show-outstanding-spirit-to-beat-bulls/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
